<resources>
    <string-array name="highscores_display">
        <item>100</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>25</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="eventTitles">
        <item>This will never occur (ideally)</item>
        <item>INCREASED VEGETATION</item>
        <item>INCREASED PREY</item>
        <item>HEAT WAVE</item>
        <item>COLD SNAP</item>
        <item>INCREASED PREDATOR PRESENCE</item>
        <item>MONSOON</item>
        <item>NUCLEAR POWER PLANT MELTDOWN</item>
        <item>PANDEMIC</item>
        <item>LOVE IS IN THE AIR</item>
        <item>CRASHED CARGO SHIP</item>
        <item>PLANT LIFE BLIGHT</item>
        <item>PREY VANISHES</item>
        <item>TWINS!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="eventMessages">
        <item>Nothing has happened. We thought we should let you know.</item>
        <item>Something is causing the wild vegetation to grow at a faster rate.  There will be more plant life for the Birbs to eat for a few generations </item>
        <item>Small animals appear to be more plentiful.  The Carnivorous Birbs will have more food for a few generations.</item>
        <item>A heat wave is making its way through this area.  The temperature will be higher for a few generations.</item>
        <item>A cold snap has struck this area.  The temperature will be lower for a few generations.</item>
        <item>A pack of roving predators have arrived area.  They appear hungry.</item>
        <item>A Monsoon has arrived! There will be flooding.  Better hope the birbs can swim!</item>
        <item>A catastrophe as struck! After a violent explosion, radioactive fallout will cause the birbs to mutate at a faster rate (for better or for worse).</item>
        <item>The Birb Flu has begun affecting the population of birbs.  Nothing they can do except ride it out for a few generations.</item>
        <item>Something in the air is causing the birbs to reproduce more, these few generations will be known as the "Birby Boomers"</item>
        <item>A cargo ship has crashed in this location!  Should the birbs investigate the ship or leave it alone?</item>
        <item>Something is now killing the vegetation in the area.  The birbs will have a hard time obtaining non-meat food.</item>
        <item>Something has killed many of the small animals the carnivorous birbs like to hunt.  They will have a hard time finding food.</item>
        <item>Two birbs gave birth to twins! Two birbs were born instead of one for this pair!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="eventPositive">
        <item>Something Broke</item>
        <item>GREAT!</item>
        <item>GREAT!</item>
        <item>That\'s Fine</item>
        <item>That\'s Fine</item>
        <item>This is REALLY not okay</item>
        <item>That\'s Fine</item>
        <item>I needed a change anyway</item>
        <item>Hope they have masks!</item>
        <item>More the Merrier!</item>
        <item>Mess with ship</item>
        <item>This is REALLY bad</item>
        <item>This is REALLY bad</item>
        <item>We can\'t support two!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="eventNegative">
        <item>Something broke</item>
        <item>Okay</item>
        <item>Okay</item>
        <item>Oh No!</item>
        <item>Oh No!</item>
        <item>This is not okay</item>
        <item>Oh No!</item>
        <item>This ruins everything!</item>
        <item>They\'ll get over it</item>
        <item>This is problematic</item>
        <item>Don\'t mess with ship</item>
        <item>This is pretty bad</item>
        <item>This is pretty bad</item>
        <item>Ah the miracle of life</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>